[
  {
    "question": "What planet is Luke Skywalker from?",
    "answer": "Tatooine",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Hoth",
      "Jakku",
      "Alderaan"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is Han Solo's best friend and copilot?",
    "answer": "Chewbacca",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "R2-D2",
      "C-3PO",
      "BB-8"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What species is Yoda?",
    "answer": "A Jedi Master of the species 'Unknown' ",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Ewok",
      "Wookiee",
      "Jawa"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Who killed Jabba the Hutt?",
    "answer": "Princess Leia",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Luke Skywalker",
      "Han Solo",
      "Darth Vader"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is Darth Vader's master?",
    "answer": "Emperor Palpatine",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Count Dooku",
      "General Grievous",
      "Kylo Ren"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of Boba Fett's ship?",
    "answer": "Slave I",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Ebon Hawk",
      "Millennium Falcon",
      "TIE Fighter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is Mace Windu's lightsaber?",
    "answer": "Purple",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Blue",
      "Green",
      "Red"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the furry creatures on Endor?",
    "answer": "Ewoks",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Womp rats",
      "Tauntauns",
      "Banthas"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which planet has the Death Star destroyed?",
    "answer": "Alderaan",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Dagobah",
      "Bespin",
      "Yavin 4"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Who trained Obi-Wan Kenobi?",
    "answer": "Qui-Gon Jinn",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Darth Maul",
      "Dooku",
      "Palpatine"
    ]
  }
]